[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Where do you feel this debate now is in America?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "feel", "this", "debate", "now", "is", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I don't know on that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What do you hope to achieve by what happens tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "to", "achieve", "by", "what", "happens", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I hope to achieve, for people to be responsible fully for what weapons they own.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "to", "achieve", ",", "for", "people", "to", "be", "responsible", "fully", "for", "what", "weapons", "they", "own", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Yes, but why do you want your pizzeria full of people armed to the teeth?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "why", "do", "you", "want", "your", "pizzeria", "full", "of", "people", "armed", "to", "the", "teeth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "It actually makes me feel more safe.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "actually", "makes", "me", "feel", "more", "safe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "It makes me feel more safe because these are responsible people.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "makes", "me", "feel", "more", "safe", "because", "these", "are", "responsible", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "So people who could walk on their own two feet and who can drive a car are not mentally ill or criminals?", "question_tokens": ["So", "people", "who", "could", "walk", "on", "their", "own", "two", "feet", "and", "who", "can", "drive", "a", "car", "are", "not", "mentally", "ill", "or", "criminals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "They're innocent until they're proven guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "innocent", "until", "they", "'re", "proven", "guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "-- to the Second Amendment?", "question_tokens": ["--", "to", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "I think it's being eroded.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "being", "eroded", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Do you know anybody that he's asked to remove their gun, to confiscate their gun?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "anybody", "that", "he", "'s", "asked", "to", "remove", "their", "gun", ",", "to", "confiscate", "their", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Personally, I don't know them.", "answer_tokens": ["Personally", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "You are quite happy for American civilians to march into your restaurant with rocket launchers, arriving in armed tanks and perhaps carrying a few Uzi submachine guns, is that your position?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "quite", "happy", "for", "American", "civilians", "to", "march", "into", "your", "restaurant", "with", "rocket", "launchers", ",", "arriving", "in", "armed", "tanks", "and", "perhaps", "carrying", "a", "few", "Uzi", "submachine", "guns", ",", "is", "that", "your", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, the thing is I don't trust our government.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "thing", "is", "I", "do", "n't", "trust", "our", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "How are they going to do that, with the American military or without the American military?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "going", "to", "do", "that", ",", "with", "the", "American", "military", "or", "without", "the", "American", "military", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, it really isn't our government that I'm worried about, it's something bigger than our government.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "really", "is", "n't", "our", "government", "that", "I", "'m", "worried", "about", ",", "it", "'s", "something", "bigger", "than", "our", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Which part of the world do you imagine is right now marshaling its troops to invade America?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "part", "of", "the", "world", "do", "you", "imagine", "is", "right", "now", "marshaling", "its", "troops", "to", "invade", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I'm not saying they are going to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "they", "are", "going", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "How many of your customers share your views, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "your", "customers", "share", "your", "views", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I couldn't tell you a number on that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "n't", "tell", "you", "a", "number", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "MD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "And that's why you're doing it, to make money, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "why", "you", "'re", "doing", "it", ",", "to", "make", "money", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I am trying to make money because that will -- how it's supposed to work is I can save money, and then I could use it later in life to support me when I put my work into society.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "trying", "to", "make", "money", "because", "that", "will", "--", "how", "it", "'s", "supposed", "to", "work", "is", "I", "can", "save", "money", ",", "and", "then", "I", "could", "use", "it", "later", "in", "life", "to", "support", "me", "when", "I", "put", "my", "work", "into", "society", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "How many people have been shot in your restaurant since you've owned it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "have", "been", "shot", "in", "your", "restaurant", "since", "you", "'ve", "owned", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Zero.", "answer_tokens": ["Zero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "I mean, putting aside this particular case, wouldn't you as a compassionate lawyer just feel that this is just not working?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "putting", "aside", "this", "particular", "case", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "as", "a", "compassionate", "lawyer", "just", "feel", "that", "this", "is", "just", "not", "working", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I'm not saying I agree that justifiable homicides have increased.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "saying", "I", "agree", "that", "justifiable", "homicides", "have", "increased", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Do you feel in the end that it will be seen as that once the trial has been and gone?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "in", "the", "end", "that", "it", "will", "be", "seen", "as", "that", "once", "the", "trial", "has", "been", "and", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "First of all, we're countering it by trying to get out more of the information that should have been out at the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "we", "'re", "countering", "it", "by", "trying", "to", "get", "out", "more", "of", "the", "information", "that", "should", "have", "been", "out", "at", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Are you confident from everything that you know that in the end George Zimmerman will be seen not to have done that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "confident", "from", "everything", "that", "you", "know", "that", "in", "the", "end", "George", "Zimmerman", "will", "be", "seen", "not", "to", "have", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I believe so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "-- and now suddenly is gripping everyone, what do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "now", "suddenly", "is", "gripping", "everyone", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, listen, this is a triple-X-rated case.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "listen", ",", "this", "is", "a", "triple-X-rated", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "So is she really doing a disservice to all women who are truly battered, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["So", "is", "she", "really", "doing", "a", "disservice", "to", "all", "women", "who", "are", "truly", "battered", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Well, let's take a listen to some of the stuff today, which was pretty gruesome, compelling, whatever you want to call it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "take", "a", "listen", "to", "some", "of", "the", "stuff", "today", ",", "which", "was", "pretty", "gruesome", ",", "compelling", ",", "whatever", "you", "want", "to", "call", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Do you think somebody who masturbates to pictures of little boys is beautiful on the inside, right?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "somebody", "who", "masturbates", "to", "pictures", "of", "little", "boys", "is", "beautiful", "on", "the", "inside", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I don't think that aspect of him is beautiful at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "aspect", "of", "him", "is", "beautiful", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "It says, \"Travis, you're beautiful on the inside and out,\" doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "says", ",", "``", "Travis", ",", "you", "'re", "beautiful", "on", "the", "inside", "and", "out", ",", "''", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", ",", "''", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "You were the one that had the KY or brought it into the relationship to make it better, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "the", "one", "that", "had", "the", "KY", "or", "brought", "it", "into", "the", "relationship", "to", "make", "it", "better", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "To facilitate our activities.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "facilitate", "our", "activities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Which one is it?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, when he jizzes on my face and throws candy my way and walks away without a word, it kind of feels like I was a prostitute.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "he", "jizzes", "on", "my", "face", "and", "throws", "candy", "my", "way", "and", "walks", "away", "without", "a", "word", ",", "it", "kind", "of", "feels", "like", "I", "was", "a", "prostitute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "But am I missing something?", "question_tokens": ["But", "am", "I", "missing", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "No, I don't think you're missing anything at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "'re", "missing", "anything", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "This is the point that I think will anger many women, is that if she is lying through her back teeth, using the cover of somehow being this poor innocent victim of a domestically violent man is really appalling, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "point", "that", "I", "think", "will", "anger", "many", "women", ",", "is", "that", "if", "she", "is", "lying", "through", "her", "back", "teeth", ",", "using", "the", "cover", "of", "somehow", "being", "this", "poor", "innocent", "victim", "of", "a", "domestically", "violent", "man", "is", "really", "appalling", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "It is appalling, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "appalling", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Are they damaging their case by putting her up there for too long?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "damaging", "their", "case", "by", "putting", "her", "up", "there", "for", "too", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "You know, there are two issues that are really being presented at the same time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "are", "two", "issues", "that", "are", "really", "being", "presented", "at", "the", "same", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Would we be going even remotely as far as we are if she wasn't there on our television screens, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "we", "be", "going", "even", "remotely", "as", "far", "as", "we", "are", "if", "she", "was", "n't", "there", "on", "our", "television", "screens", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, she is very mesmerizing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "is", "very", "mesmerizing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "It comes down to this, is this guy just fantasizing or is there enough evidence to suggest he was really planning to do this?", "question_tokens": ["It", "comes", "down", "to", "this", ",", "is", "this", "guy", "just", "fantasizing", "or", "is", "there", "enough", "evidence", "to", "suggest", "he", "was", "really", "planning", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "That's what the jurors basically are going to have to decide.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "the", "jurors", "basically", "are", "going", "to", "have", "to", "decide", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Because in reality if they cannot prove that he was genuinely going to do this, then presumably he will walk, won't he?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "in", "reality", "if", "they", "can", "not", "prove", "that", "he", "was", "genuinely", "going", "to", "do", "this", ",", "then", "presumably", "he", "will", "walk", ",", "wo", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, I teach about these cases in my criminal law class and I write about them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "teach", "about", "these", "cases", "in", "my", "criminal", "law", "class", "and", "I", "write", "about", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Let me bring in Gloria there, because it seems to me that even if he wasn't going to carry out these appalling crimes, the mere fact he's put these women, including his wife and female friends, through this appalling psychological trauma, that they must be reading about this sickening plot that he was e-mailing people about, is that not in itself a crime?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "bring", "in", "Gloria", "there", ",", "because", "it", "seems", "to", "me", "that", "even", "if", "he", "was", "n't", "going", "to", "carry", "out", "these", "appalling", "crimes", ",", "the", "mere", "fact", "he", "'s", "put", "these", "women", ",", "including", "his", "wife", "and", "female", "friends", ",", "through", "this", "appalling", "psychological", "trauma", ",", "that", "they", "must", "be", "reading", "about", "this", "sickening", "plot", "that", "he", "was", "e-mailing", "people", "about", ",", "is", "that", "not", "in", "itself", "a", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "EX", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "LLRED: Not really just to worry them, but having said that --", "answer_tokens": ["LLRED", ":", "Not", "really", "just", "to", "worry", "them", ",", "but", "having", "said", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Isn't that abuse to his wife?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "abuse", "to", "his", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "There are more details.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "more", "details", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "You know, it was five years pretty much from beginning to end.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "five", "years", "pretty", "much", "from", "beginning", "to", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What is your reaction to the reaction so far?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "reaction", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, you know, it's tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "But did you think that the president had a point there, that perhaps the Canadians in the movie version didn't get quite enough of the credit they probably deserved?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "think", "that", "the", "president", "had", "a", "point", "there", ",", "that", "perhaps", "the", "Canadians", "in", "the", "movie", "version", "did", "n't", "get", "quite", "enough", "of", "the", "credit", "they", "probably", "deserved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I think that's always true.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "always", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Do you think that your husband deserves all the adulation that's being showered upon him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "your", "husband", "deserves", "all", "the", "adulation", "that", "'s", "being", "showered", "upon", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I'm always ready to jump in there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "always", "ready", "to", "jump", "in", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130226pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]